familyguyepisodes.tv 2014-05-15

# Watch Full Length Family Guy Episodes Online - Privacy Policy

  | 

|    
|  |    

**This site is owned by FamilyGuyEpisodes.TV. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At FamilyGuyEpisodes.TV, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe. We feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of your information. This privacy statement discloses what and how information is gathered.**

**FamilyGuyEpisodes.TV does not collect any personal information such as name and email addresses from users except for those leaving episode reviews and comments. In addition, this site contains external links to other websites, and is monitized by advertisement. FamilyGuyEpisodes.TV is not responsible and has no control over the content and privacy policy of those websites should a user follow a link or advertisement to said website.**

** Reviews/Comment Privacy Notice This policy contains information relating to your privacy when submitting a comment. By submitting a comment, you are declaring that you understand this policy: 

  * Your name, website address, town, country, rating and comment will be publicly displayed if entered.
  * Aside from the data entered into these form fields, other stored data about your comment will include: 
    * Your IP Address (not displayed)
    * The time/date of your submission (displayed)
  * Your email address will not be shared. It is collected for only two reasons: 
    * Administrative purposes, should a need to contact you arise.
    * To inform you of new comments, should you subscribe to receive notifications.
  * A cookie may be set on your computer. This is used to remember your inputs. It will expire by itself after a certain period of time.

This policy is subject to change at any time and without notice. **  
  
---|---
